Deleting an odd and linked list.
We need to create a new method called of delete known.
It took struct known, had reference and that and key.
So we have think about this.
This link at last we have three nods.
100, 200 and 300.
The data so struck note.
We are creating a temporary node if had a different data, equal, equal to key.
So we are searching for the key.
We need to detect if the key exists.
OK, so if it were to key, then dump equal to had and had equal to the next and free, then what does
this mean?
This would execute by creating the key equal to 100 because we are passing day equal to 100.
Think about we are going to delete the node that contains the key equal to 100 or the data equal to
one.
OK, we start by searching for this.
OK.
It's on the head.
So.
This had this is the had so if had data equal, equal to key, then it is the first element.
OK.
OK, guys.
And these are the references of the next not so create them equal equal to had had equal to the reference
than the next and then the free time freed them means they lead the.
Elements, OK, they lead, they're not.
You see, guys, I will repeat it.
OK, so.
We have detected that a key equal to the head.
Now, but it changed at the time.
You see, guys, how we changed the temp and temp remove free the temp.
OK.
This is very simple.
We are deleting it.
And now the had the references to the 2024.
And it is the starting and the beginning of the link, at least.
So we have deleted that.
Not at the beginning.
No.
Let's see another example.
If had the data that what took, we know the key now equal to 200, we are searching for it, then that
contains the head that contains the data equal to 200.
So we start the first one is not the case.
So if had the equity took, no.
So we will create a not thecurrent, we change it to the head and the curtain.
And while current next does not equal to null, we start by searching for the link for the key.
So if we find it like here, then data equal, equal to key, then temp equal to the current and next.
So now it is the temp.
Then.
Current next equal current next and next next.
I am making getting the reference of that stamp.
The next of the stamp and put it putting it inside the current.
So she goes, it's very important.
See the animation.
And follow me, I am putting that not that it is next to that stamp, which is three thousand twenty
four.
I'm copying the index and putting it inside that current.
I'm changing.
You see, guys, what we have changed, we are getting that reference of there.
Not that that is next to that.
It is three thousand twenty four and replacing it with the index of that car, OK, after this three
the stamp.
So I'm freeing that term by removing the stamp and making now directly and braking.
So the question now is detecting and referencing the the next not that it was the next note of the stamp.
You see, guys, it's very important don their stamp this.